https://pureprescriptions.com/privacy-policy/

Skip to content
Health LibraryHealth A-ZDrug InteractionsHealth ConditionsHealth NewsWireVitamins & HerbsHealth GuidesVitamins & HerbsDiet SupplementsFitness SupplementsHomeopathySupplements A to ZHealth ConditionsDiabetesAllergiesHealth ToolsConditions A to ZDiet & FitnessWeight ManagementJoint & Soft Tissue ConditionsObesity: Need to KnowRxAnswersLearn About InteractionsLipitorMedicines A to ZZoloftHealthMen’s HealthWomen’s HealthChildren’s HealthAging Gracefully CloseBlogAbout UsOur StoryMission & TeamContact UsWholesaleAmbassador Program Close
Search for:
0
Privacy Statement
This statement describes the privacy practices for the PurePrescriptions.com website. PurePrescriptions® is a fully owned subsidiary of Pure Prescriptions, Inc.. PurePrescriptions® is committed to protecting the privacy of our valued customers.
PurePrescriptions® privacy policy notifies you of the information we collect from you during your use of our site, how that information is used, the organizations and people with whom we may share that information and what choices are available to you in regards to the collection, use and distribution of the information. This policy also details the security procedures in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under PurePrescriptions’ control, and how you can change, or correct inaccuracies in, your personal information.
Pure Prescriptions, Inc. is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others, other than as described in “Sharing” below.
If you feel that we are not abiding by our posted privacy policy, you should Contact Us.
Information Collected During Registration Process
By registering with PurePrescriptions®, users receive access to our website, including online ordering. We will not sell, share, or rent your information to others, other than as described in “Sharing” below.
Information Collected When You Place an Order
When an order is placed, the user must provide contact information (such as name and shipping address) and financial information (such as credit card number). This information is used for billing purposes and to fill customer’s orders. If we have trouble processing an order, this contact information is used to get in touch with the user. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others, other than as described in “Sharing” below.
Cookies
A cookie is a piece of data stored on a user’s hard drive containing information about the user. Cookies are used on our website to save the user time and effort; for example, the use of cookies enables the Remember Me option, which allows the user access to specific information without having to login each time. Cookies can also remember the last page or position you visited, which can be very helpful if you have opened numerous pages of information. If a browser is not set up to accept cookies, users will not be able to use the restricted portion of our site. We do not sell, share or rent any information obtained through the use of cookies.
Log Files
We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.
Sharing
We use a outside credit card processing company to bill users for goods and services. These companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes.
We may also contact you from time to time with promotions, review requests, and voluntary surveys to gather information to better serve you.
Security Technology
This website takes every precaution to protect your information. When users submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline. When sensitive information (such as a credit card number) is required, that information is encrypted and is protected with the best encryption software in the industry – SSL. While on a secure page, such as our order form, the lock icon on the bottom of Web browsers becomes locked, as opposed to unlocked.
While we use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, we also do everything in our power to protect user-information offline. All of our users’ information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, a customer service representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information. Furthermore, ALL employees are kept up-to-date on our security and privacy practices. Finally, the servers that we store personally identifiable information on are kept in a secure environment protected by the latest firewall technology.
If you have any questions about the security at our website, please Contact Us.
Contacting You
We send all new customers and newsletter subscribers a welcome email along with occasional promotions and education emails.Out of respect for the privacy of our users, we present the option to not receive these emails or newsletters. Please see Choice/Opt-out below.
Correcting/Updating Personal Information
If a user’s personally identifiable information changes (such as your address or telephone number), there are several options available. Information can be changed, updated or deleted by visiting the My Account section of this website, by emailing us, or by calling us and talking to one of our Customer Service Representatives. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others, except as detailed in “Sharing” above.
Choice/Opt-out/Opt-in
Users who no longer wish to receive our e-newsletter and related information may opt-out of receiving these communications by simply selecting the Unsubscribe link at the bottom of any email we send.
Your Consent/Notification of Changes
By using www.PurePrescriptions.com, you consent to our collection and use of your information as described here in this Privacy Policy. This policy may be amended from time to time.
Home
About Us
Our Team & Mission
FAQ + Contact Us
Privacy
Terms
Wholesale
*These statements have not been evaluated by the FDA. Products are not intended to diagnose, treat, cure or prevent any disease.
Results may vary© Pure Prescriptions, Inc.
2020
Search for:
What’s New
Shop
Departments
Men’s Health
Women’s Health
Children’s Health
Essential Oils
Heart Health
Shop by Manufacturer Brand
Allergy Research Group (11)Argentyn 23 (1)Ayush Herbs (2)Bubs Naturals (2)Collagen M.D. (1)DaVinci Labs (21)Designs for Health (96)Douglas Laboratories (33)Dr. Christopher's (7)Econugenics (1)Enada (2)Enzyme Science (4)Even (2)Genestra (69)Genicel Inc (1)Greens First (9)Holley Pharmaceuticals (1)Iagen Professional (9)Integrative Therapeutics, Inc. (46)Interplexus, Inc. (3)Jigsaw Health, LLC (1)Klean Athlete (13)Lab ServicesLeucadia Health (1)N. American Herb & Spice (1)NewGreens (5)Nordic Naturals Pro (33)Optimox (1)Oxylent (3)Physician's Strength (2)Prof Birkmayer (1)ProLon (1)Protocol For Life (13)Prüvit (1)Pure Encapsulations (397)Pure Prescriptions (24)Pure Wellness Pack (1)Quality Of Life Labs (1)ReNew Life (2)Ruved (2)Sarati (4)Sports Illustrated™ Nutrition (10)Tango Advanced Nutrition (9)Thorne Research (58)Ultima Replenisher (2)Unda (140)Vinco (2)Vital Nutrients (45)Vitamin IQ (6)Wakunaga (1)Well Wisdom (1)Whole Journey (3)Young Living (18)
Brand Image bottom
Pure Prescriptions
Health Library
Health A-Z
Drug Interactions
Health Conditions
Health NewsWire
Vitamins & Herbs
Aging Gracefully
[Row]
health-img
health-img
health-img
Blog
About Us
Our Story
Mission & Team
Contact Us
Log in
Lost your password?
Register
Email address *
Password *
Your personal data will be used to support your experience throughout this website, to manage access to your account, and for other purposes described in our privacy policy.
Register
Skip to content
Open toolbar
Accessibility Tools
Increase Text
Decrease Text
Grayscale
High Contrast
Please inititate a chat below or call 760-688-3199 to access the Wholesale Signup Page.
